http://www.grandvision.org/privacy-policy.asp

Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to GrandVision.org:
* We don't ask you for personal information unless we
need it.
* We don't share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
* We don't store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.
Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals:
Website Visitors
Like most website operators, GrandVision.org collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. GrandVision.org's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how GrandVision.org's visitors use its website. From time to time, GrandVision.org may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.
GrandVision.org does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.
GrandVision.org also collects potentially personally-identifying information such as Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, to discourage spammers.
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to GrandVision.org's website choose to interact with GrandVision.org in ways that require GrandVision.org to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that GrandVision.org gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account to provide an email address. Those who engage in transactions with GrandVision.org are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, GrandVision.org collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with GrandVision.org. GrandVision.org does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.
Aggregated Statistics
GrandVision.org may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website. For instance, GrandVision.org may monitor the most popular accounts. GrandVision.org may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, GrandVision.org does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.
Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information
GrandVision.org discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on GrandVision.org's behalf or to provide services available at GrandVision.org's website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using GrandVision.org's website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. GrandVision.org will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, GrandVision.org discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when GrandVision.org believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of GrandVision.org, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a GrandVision.org website and have supplied your email address, GrandVision.org may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with GrandVision.org and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. GrandVision.org takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.
Cookies
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. GrandVision.org may use cookies to help GrandVision.org identify and track visitors, their usage of GrandVision.org's website, and their website access preferences. GrandVision.org visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using GrandVision.org's website, with the drawback that certain features of GrandVision.org's website may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
Privacy Policy ChangesAlthough most changes are likely to be minor, GrandVision.org may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in GrandVision.org's sole discretion. GrandVision.org encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a GrandVision.org account, you should also check the dashboard for alerts to these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
Contact Us
Site Map
Terms & Conditions
Privacy Policy
Photo Credits
Webmaster
Home
© 2014 Grand Vision Foundation. All rights reserved.
Grand Vision Foundation & Grand Annex, 434 W. 6th St., San Pedro, CA 90731 (310) 833-4813
Warner Grand Theatre, 478 W. 6th St., San Pedro, CA 90731 (310) 548-2493
The Warner Grand Theatre is a facility of the CIty of Los Angeles Dept. of Cultural Affairs.
